{
    "subject": "resource/The_Smiling_Lieutenant",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Maurice_Chevalier",
    "human_readable": "The Smiling Lieutenant stars Maurice Chevalier.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.91557776927948,
            "question": "Are there any other films starring Maurice Chevalier besides 'The Smiling Lieutenant'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8473696708679199,
            "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Smiling Lieutenant'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7322089672088623,
            "question": "Can you name a film starring Maurice Chevalier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6594613790512085,
            "question": "Is Maurice Chevalier known for acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5634608864784241,
            "question": "Was Maurice Chevalier a famous actor during his time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5496139526367188,
            "question": "What genre is likely the movie 'The Smiling Lieutenant'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5443653464317322,
            "question": "Who are some other famous actors from the same period as Maurice Chevalier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5094442963600159,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie featuring Maurice Chevalier?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4832282066345215,
            "question": "What type of roles did Maurice Chevalier typically play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4312571883201599,
            "question": "What era was Maurice Chevalier popular in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Smiling Lieutenant stars Maurice Chevalier.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7613_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of roles did Maurice Chevalier typically play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7613_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the movie featuring Maurice Chevalier?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7613_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other famous actors from the same period as Maurice Chevalier?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7613_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7613_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7613_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7613_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7613_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7613_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7613_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7613_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7613_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7613_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7613_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about the cast of \"The Smiling Lieutenant,\" including Maurice Chevalier, which supports the statement that he starred in the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}